<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
	<title>All - naacl.org</title>
	<link></link>
	<description>
		All - for the North American Chapter of the Association for Computational Linguistics: NAACL. 
	</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 15:15:10 +0800</lastBuildDate>

	
<item>
	<title>JSALT Summer School Scholarship</title>
	<description>
	&lt;p&gt;NAACL is excited to fund a limited number of undergraduate students to
attend the two-week summer school at the 2018 Jelinek Summer Workshop
on Speech and Language Technology. Apply by Monday, April 30, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/calls/summerschool/2018/index.html&quot;&gt;Read more »&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

	</description>
	<guid>//posts/2018-04-09-JSALT-Summer-School-Scholarship</guid>
	<link>//posts/2018-04-09-JSALT-Summer-School-Scholarship</link>
	<pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
	<title>2018 NAACL Emerging Regions Fund Call for Proposals</title>
	<description>
	&lt;p&gt;The goal of the NAACL Emerging Regions fund is to assist the creation of a larger and more cohesive Computational Linguistics community in Latin America, and to enhance more regional interactions among students and researchers anywhere in the Americas. The deadline for proposals is 30 April 2018 for events to take place between June 2018 and June 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/calls/emerging_regions/2018/index.html&quot;&gt;Read more »&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

	</description>
	<guid>//posts/2018-04-01-2018-NAACL-Emerging-Regions-Fund-Call-for-Proposals</guid>
	<link>//posts/2018-04-01-2018-NAACL-Emerging-Regions-Fund-Call-for-Proposals</link>
	<pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Results of the NAACL Board Elections</title>
	<description>
	&lt;p&gt;The results of the NAACL Board elections are in. Here are the newly elected officers for 2018, including 3 new board members as per last year’s constitutional amendment:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://juliahmr.cs.illinois.edu/&quot;&gt;Julia Hockenmaier&lt;/a&gt; (Chair)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sites.google.com/site/colinacherry/&quot;&gt;Colin Cherry&lt;/a&gt; (Secretary)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ling.ohio-state.edu/~demarneffe.1/&quot;&gt;Marie-Catherine de Marneffe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://users.soe.ucsc.edu/~maw/&quot;&gt;Marilyn Walker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cs.washington.edu/people/faculty/lsz&quot;&gt;Luke Zettlemoyer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and joining the board as the new ACL treasurer, we have:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cs.jhu.edu/~yarowsky/&quot;&gt;David Yarowsky&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to Hal Daumé III and Graeme Hirst, who have finished their service on the NAACL executive board, and to the nominating committee, chaired by Katrin Erk. Thanks also to everyone who voted in this year’s NAACL Board elections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/officers/officers-2018.html&quot;&gt;Take a look at the 2018 NAACL Board »&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

	</description>
	<guid>//posts/2018-01-07-Results-of-the-NAACL-Board-Elections</guid>
	<link>//posts/2018-01-07-Results-of-the-NAACL-Board-Elections</link>
	<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
	<title>2018 NAACL Board Election Candidates</title>
	<description>
	&lt;p&gt;Candidate statements for the 2018 NAACL Board Elections have been posted &lt;a href=&quot;/elections/2018/index.html&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, along with instructions on how to submit additional nominations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/elections/2018/index.html&quot;&gt;Read more »&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

	</description>
	<guid>//posts/2017-09-28-2018-NAACL-Board-Election-Candidates</guid>
	<link>//posts/2017-09-28-2018-NAACL-Board-Election-Candidates</link>
	<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
	<title>2017 NAACL Emerging Regions Fund Call for Proposals</title>
	<description>
	&lt;p&gt;The goal of the NAACL Emerging Regions fund is to assist the creation of a larger and more cohesive Computational Linguistics community in Latin America, and to enhance more regional interactions among students and researchers anywhere in the Americas. The deadline for proposals is 30 April 2017 (midnight PST) for events to take place between June 2017 and June 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/calls/emerging_regions/2017/index.html&quot;&gt;Read more »&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

	</description>
	<guid>//posts/2017-03-20-2017-NAACL-Emerging-Regions-Fund-Call-for-Proposals</guid>
	<link>//posts/2017-03-20-2017-NAACL-Emerging-Regions-Fund-Call-for-Proposals</link>
	<pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
	<title>New NAACL Board Members</title>
	<description>
	&lt;p&gt;The results of the NAACL Board elections are in. The newly elected Board members for 2017 are:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cs.rochester.edu/~tetreaul/academic.html&quot;&gt;Joel Tetreault&lt;/a&gt; (Treasurer)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cs.utah.edu/~riloff/&quot;&gt;Ellen Riloff&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.umiacs.umd.edu/~resnik/&quot;&gt;Philip Resnik&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The constitutional amendment to add a fifth member to the board has passed and will take effect for the next NAACL election cycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to Matt Post and Fei Xia, who have finished their service on the NAACL executive board, and to the nominating committee, chaired by Mona Diab. Thanks also to everyone who voted in this year’s NAACL Board elections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/officers/officers-2017.html&quot;&gt;Take a look at the 2017 NAACL Board »&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/policies/constitution.html&quot;&gt;Take a look at the amended constitution »&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

	</description>
	<guid>//posts/2017-01-03-New-NAACL-Board-Members</guid>
	<link>//posts/2017-01-03-New-NAACL-Board-Members</link>
	<pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
	<title>2017 NAACL Board Election Candidates</title>
	<description>
	&lt;p&gt;Candidate statements for the 2017 NAACL Board Elections have been posted &lt;a href=&quot;/elections/2017/index.html&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, along with instructions on how to submit additional nominations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/elections/2017/index.html&quot;&gt;Read more »&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

	</description>
	<guid>//posts/2016-09-19-NAACL-2017-Election-Announcement-and-Call-for-Additional-Nominations</guid>
	<link>//posts/2016-09-19-NAACL-2017-Election-Announcement-and-Call-for-Additional-Nominations</link>
	<pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Recipients of 2016 NAACL Emerging Regions Fund Award</title>
	<description>
	&lt;p&gt;We are excited to announce the two recipients of the 2016 NAACL &lt;a href=&quot;calls/emerging_regions/index.html&quot;&gt;Emerging Regions Fund Award&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Federal University of Juiz de Fora, to support a theme session of Computational Semantics with Frames and Constructions.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The Instituto Caro y Cuervo and Universidad Nacional de Colombia, for the organization of a national meeting of researchers of Computational Linguistics and Corpus Linguistics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both recipients will receive $1,500 USD. This year was a particularly competitive year as we had a record number of submissions (11).&lt;/p&gt;

	</description>
	<guid>//posts/2016-06-24-Recipients-of-2016-NAACL-Emerging-Regions-Fund-Award</guid>
	<link>//posts/2016-06-24-Recipients-of-2016-NAACL-Emerging-Regions-Fund-Award</link>
	<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
	<title>NLP in Latin America Survey</title>
	<description>
	&lt;p&gt;If you are a researcher in Natural Language Processing from or in
Latin America (as defined as Central America, South America and the
Caribbean), we want to get your feedback and opinions on what role, if
any, NAACL could play in helping grow NLP in Latin America.  To this
end, we circulated this survey this winter, but understand some people
might not have yet had an opportunity to fill it out.  If you meet the
requirements, please fill it out (links below) by July 30, 2016.  We
are compiling the feedback and will share it as a report later this
summer.  The survey will take you about 10 minutes to complete.  We
have translated the survey into three languages (English, Portuguese
and Spanish); please feel free to use whichever form you are most
comfortable with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1mL_sNShyZ2I2rj9HEiWBzKOf-Egft-zSUgLJGtNmMXs/viewform&quot;&gt;English&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/149Z8_EzTHSs_ur-P51VlSL0NzfJNF-OS__ktYt-6FHw/viewform&quot;&gt;Portuguese&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1gMN3JJYwIOlbMJZ9PCpRCgiYzmtF87rpJI3wzVymWB8/viewform&quot;&gt;Spanish&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, as we want to reach as many researchers in the region as
possible, we would appreciate it if you could forward the link to your
colleagues we might have missed inadvertently, or provide us with
their email addresses so we can contact them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your time!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Joel Tetreault, Yahoo &lt;br /&gt;
Fei Xia, University of Washington&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Special thanks to members of the Latin American NLP community and the
NAACL Board for their help in designing the survey.  And thanks to
Valeria de Paiva, Carla Parra Escartín and Paloma de Juan for the
translations.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

	</description>
	<guid>//posts/2016-06-23-NLP-in-Latin-America-Survey</guid>
	<link>//posts/2016-06-23-NLP-in-Latin-America-Survey</link>
	<pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
	<title>Crowdsourcing START suggestions</title>
	<description>
	&lt;p&gt;The NAACL board is currently crowdsourcing feature requests for START, the tool used to manage the proceedings of *ACL conferences. Softconf, the company that built and maintains START, has built a very nice tool around our community’s extensive custom tools for producing our own proceedings; however, many of these interfaces could stand for some UI and UX improvement. Softconf has been very accommodating with different changes here and there over the years, and we plan to collect a large set of ideas for improvements and work with them on an overhaul.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please visit this page to contribute your suggestions and feature requests: 
&lt;a href=&quot;http://tinyurl.com/start-wishlist&quot;&gt;http://tinyurl.com/start-wishlist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

	</description>
	<guid>//posts/2016-06-15-Crowdsourcing-START-suggestions</guid>
	<link>//posts/2016-06-15-Crowdsourcing-START-suggestions</link>
	<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>



</channel>
</rss>
